Preliminary Inventory to the College Republican National Committee Records, 1967-1974.
Hoover Institution Archives
College Republican National Committee Records,
1967-1974.
85009
College Republican National Committee.
51 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize box (22.6 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Correspondence, memoranda, minutes, financial records, campaign material, and printed matter, relating to student involvement in Republican political activity.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1985.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Access Points
Republican Party (U.S.: 1854-); Student movements--United States.; Universities and colleges--United States.; United States--Politics and government.; United States--Politics and government--1963-1969.; United States--Politics and government--1969-1974.
Container List
- Container List
  - State files - 1972 (Box 1)
    - Alabama-Georgia
    - Hawaii-Kansas (Box 2)
    - Kentucky-Montana (Box 3)
    - Nebraska-North Dakota (Box 4)
    - Ohio-South Dakota (Box 5)
    - Tennessee-Virginia (Box 6)
    - Washington-Wyoming (Box 7)
  - College Republican National Committee manuals (Box 8)
  - College Republican
  - 1972 campaign literature
  - State files - 1971 (Box 9)
    - Alabama-Illinois
    - Illinois-Massachusetts (Box 10)
    - Michigan-North Dakota (Box 11)
    - Ohio-Virginia (Box 12)
    - Washington-Wyoming (Box 13)
    - Guam
  - 1974
    - Alabama-California
    - Colorado-Illinois (Box 14)
    - Illinois-Maine (Box 15)
    - Maryland-Minnesota (Box 16)
    - Mississippi-New York (Box 17)
    - North Carolina-South Dakota (Box 18)
    - Tennessee-West Virginia (Box 19)
    - Wisconsin-Wyoming (Box 20)
  - Regions and areas, 1971-1973
  - Regions and areas, 1971-1973 (Box 21)
  - Regions and areas, 1971-1973 (Box 22)
  - Student Fieldmen Schools, 1971-1973
  - Student Fieldmen Schools, 1971-1973 (Box 23)
  - Chairman's files, 1974
  - Chairman's files, 1971-1974 (Box 24)
  - Executive director's files, 1971-1974 (Box 25)
  - National officers' files, 1972-1974 (Box 26)
  - Day file, 1974 (Box 27)
  - Day file, 1974 (Box 28)
  - Day file, 1974 (Box 29)
  - Day file, 1971, 1973-1974 (Box 30)
  - Karl Rove endorsement letters
  - Organization files (Box 31)
  - Board meetings
  - Board meetings (Box 32)
  - Washington Campus News Service
  - Working files
  - Working files (Box 33)
  - Financial records
  - Financial records (Box 34)
  - Project files
  - Mailings, 1971 (Box 35)
  - Mailings, 1972-1973 (Box 36)
  - Print orders, 1971 (Box 37)
  - Print orders, 1972 (Box 38)
  - Print orders, 1974 (Box 39)
  - Print orders, 1972 (Box 40)
  - Student Fieldmen School proofs
  - Collected material (Box 41)
  - Files relating to other organizations
  - Files relating to other organizations (Box 42)
  - Files relating to other organizations (Box 43)
  - Republican National Committee, 1972 (Box 44)
  - Republican National Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 45)
  - Youth campaigns, 1967-1972 (Box 46)
  - Youth campaigns, 1967-1972 (Box 47)
  - Unsorted (Box 48)
  - Unsorted (Box 49)
  - Unsorted (Box 50)
  - Posters (Box 51)